{
    "subject": "resource/Udham_Singh",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1899-12-26",
    "human_readable": "Udham Singh was born on December 26, 1899.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9180378913879395,
            "question": "Was Udham Singh born in the 1900s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.902660608291626,
            "question": "When was Udham Singh born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9020441174507141,
            "question": "Is Udham Singh's birthday in December?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8891677856445312,
            "question": "Is Udham Singh's birthdate later than December 25th?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8684821128845215,
            "question": "What century was Udham Singh born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8585036993026733,
            "question": "If today was December 26th, would it be Udham Singh's birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7857688069343567,
            "question": "What is Udham Singh's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6767699718475342,
            "question": "What month and day was Udham Singh born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4731220006942749,
            "question": "In what year did Udham Singh come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35244470834732056,
            "question": "What information about Udham Singh is given in this statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Udham Singh was born on December 26, 1899.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1081_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Udham Singh come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1081_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What month and day was Udham Singh born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1081_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Udham Singh's birthdate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1081_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1081_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently mention that Udham Singh was born on December 26, 1899. Therefore, the statement is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}